1.) Streamlit : It is a Python library that makes the website application for Python scripts without
needing to use popular web languages like HTML or CSS.
It can be regarded as Python's own web app library.

2.) pickle : It makes files in Google Colab to store objects and to
load the objects into another platform; for example :- PyCharm.

3.) NLTK : Natural LanguageTool Kit is a library that identifies characters, words and sentences
and is used mostly in Text classification.

4.) string : This library contains the punctuation marks, stopwords used in texts.

5.) stopwords: The words that don't really have a meaning are the stopwords. Example : I, they, them, and

 6.) punkt_tab : This identifies the sentences in a text.

7.) Porter Stemmer : Object that stems the words. Example of stemming :
"loves, loved, loving" :- love
These 3 have the same meaning so they are stemmed into one word.

8.) Why are the files for the vectorizer and the model made?
Ans : Machine leaning Models, like computers, only understands binary and numbers. So, vectorizer
converts the Human readable English into Machine readable vectors of numbers.
Vectorizer is the translator that makes the model understand the human language.So,
that is why the vectorizer file is made to store that tfidf vectorizer.

The model file is made to store the model that will classify the SMS.

