Why were the SMS preprocessed?
Ans : Machine Learning Model cannot be fed unprocessed data. Like how
humans cannot eat raw food, they have to cook it; models cannot be given unprocessed data, so the data has to be
"cooked" which means processed.

Steps of SMS Preprocessing :
1. Lowercase all the texts
2. Remove the special characters
3. Remove the stopwords
4. Stemming
5. Word Tokenization

Why is Vectorization done?
Ans : Vectorization translates the human-readable English into
machine-readable binary or numbers. The Term Frequency - Inverse Document
Frequency (TF-IDF) vectorizer work comparatively better than Bag of words(BoW) vectorizer.

What does 0 and 1 stand for?
Ans : 0 means Ham and 1 means Spam because Ham comes before Spam alphabetically
and 0 comes before 1 so they were assigned sequentially.

fit_transform() : fit :- internally assign 0 to Ham and 1 to spam
                : transform :- converts Ham to 0 and spam to 1
